babylonprivate.com 2011-03-21

# Privacy policy

Personal data.   
Babylonprivate.com may require from Members to provide contact information (such as name, address, zip code, email addresses and phone numbers), financial information (this includes account or credit card numbers). Babylonprivate.com uses contact information to proof members' age and identity, or identity and age of performers within Member’s content, to send the member information needed to maintain their membership account, to contact them when necessary, and to notify them about news on Babylonprivate.com. The collected financial information is used to check the members' qualifications, to bill the member for services ordered and for payout processing.

IP Address.   
Babylonprivate.com uses member's IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer the website. IP address is used to help identify the Member and to gather broad demographic information.

Cookies.   
Babylonprivate.com uses cookies to save member’s preferences. Cookies are used to track IP address only for the purposes of tracking unique user sessions, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer Babylonprivate.com website.

Monitoring the services  
Babylonprivate.com reserves the right, but has no obligation, to monitor all services offered. This includes but is not limited to the content posted on Babylonprivate.com website and the contents of communications transmitted while engaging in voice and text chat, email, or voicemail. Babylonprivate.com shall have the right to disclose information transmitted while using its services for any reason if the Babylonprivate.com believes that it is reasonable to do so, including to: satisfy laws, regulations, or governmental or legal requests; operate the service properly; or protect itself and/or users.

Sharing of information  
The Website does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with any third party, except to the financial institution that processes your transaction (credit purchase or payouts processing). If our company goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, members personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

Release.   
Members' personal information may be released when Babylonprivate.com believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to:   
(1) comply with applicable law, regulation or subpoena;   
(2) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements; or   
(3) protect the rights, property or safety of our users and/or any third parties.
